A last report in the group of site content reports is the exit report.
网站内容报告组中的最后一个报告是退出报告
I said before that I don't think this is the most helpful report you can find here,
我之前说过 我认为这不是你可以在这里找到的最有用的报告
but now that we have talked about bounces a lot,
但是现在我们已经很多次地谈到了跳出
I want to pause and make sure we get a difference between an exit and a bounce.
我想暂停一下 并确保我们了解退出和跳出之间的差别
Remember how we said that a bounce is a visit where
请记住 我们之前说过跳出
the person left your site from the entrance page.
是指访客从入口页面离开你的网站
Basically, they enter your site and immediately leave.
基本上 他们进入你的网站并立即离开
A page is bounce rate does refers to the percentage of
页面跳出率是指
visits where this page is the only page in the session.
会话仅包括此页面的访问百分比
An exit is different,
而退出则不同
it means the user exits from this page
这意味着无论用户在该会话中访问了多少页面
regardless of how many pages the user visited in that session.
最后退出了此页面
So a bounce would be considered an exit but not every exit is a bounce.
所以 跳出会被视为退出 但不是每一个退出都是跳出
When we study pages,
当我们研究页面时
we talk about the bounce suite and the percent exits,
我们会讨论跳出率和退出百分比
and here is a refresher on the definitions.
这里是对定义的一次回顾
The bounce rate is the percentage of single page visits,
跳出率是单个页面访问的百分比
so visits in which the person left your site
也就是说 访客从入口页面离开你的网站
from the entrance page without interacting with the page.
而不会与页面进行互动
Percent exits is the number of exits
退出百分比是退出的数量
divided by the number of page views for the page or a set of pages.
除以该页面或一组页面的页面浏览次数
It indicates how often users exit from
它表示用户在浏览页面时从
that page or set of pages when they view the pages.
该页面或一组页面退出的频率
Now just so we're all clear on the difference,
现在 我们弄清楚了它们之间的区别
let's take another look at an example,
我们再来看一个例子
this time for Bamboo HR.
这次是 Bamboo HR 的例子
First, let's look at what a bounce looks like.
首先 我们来看看跳出的情况
For the sake of this example,
这个例子中
we choose the pricing page as the landing page.
我们选择了定价页面作为着陆页
And because the visitor left immediately after landing on
而且由于访客在登陆此页面后立即离开
this page without any other interaction on the page,
而没有在页面上进行任何其他互动
for instance, clicking on a link,
例如 单击一个链接
discounts towards the bounce rate for the pricing page.
这构成了定价页面的跳出率
And since the visitors came to my site and left,
并且 由于访客来到我的网站并离开
it also counts towards the exit rate for this pricing page.
它也计入了这个定价页面的退出率
Now let's take a look at an exit that's not a bounce.
现在我们来看一个不是跳出的退出情况
In this case, the landing page is the home page and the visitor goes
在这里 着陆页是主页
beyond this page interacting with it by clicking on the pricing link.
访客通过点击定价链接可跳出此页面与其互动
The visitor that lands on the pricing page and decides to exit by typing in another URL.
访客登录到定价页面并通过键入另一个 URL 退出
So discounts towards an exit for the pricing page,
这就构成了定价页面的退出
but this is not a bounce since there was more than one page in the session.
但这不是一个跳出 因为会话中有不止一个页面
As I said before,
正如我之前所说的
users need to exit at some point,
用户需要在某一时刻退出
it's normal and those exits are going to be distributed across your site.
这很正常 而且这些退出将分布在你的整个网站
However, if you see disproportional exits on pages that are part of
但是 如果你在转化或检出路径的页面上看到不成比例的退出
a conversion or check-out path or that represents a clear beginning of an action,
或者在清楚表示一次行为开始的页面上看到不成比例的退出
then you may want to take a closer look.
那么你可能要仔细查看一下
In the example we just walked through,
在我们刚刚看过的例子中
if many people are exiting from this pricing page,
如果很多人退出这个定价页面
Bamboo HR may find that it is not achieving its goals with
Bamboo HR 可能会发现这个页面没有实现它的目标
this page as it is clearly meant to get users to submit information.
因为它显然是为了让用户提交信息
In that case, they may want to test
在这种情况下 他们可能要测试
different versions of this page and see whether they would do better.
这个页面的不同版本 看看他们是否会做得更好